麦克斯 我觉得约炮软件上的这妞
Max, I feel like this woman on Tinder
在年龄上撒谎了
is lying about her age.
如果她是78岁 那我就是25岁
If she's 78, I'm 25.
我觉得年龄大概80岁 奶子大概40岁
I'd say she's 80, but that rack is 40.
我是可以把她挤进我今晚"日"程
Well, maybe I can squeeze her in tonight,
但我已经跟八个妞有约了
but I already got eight dates.
都是我这关节炎害我没法左划拒绝
With my arthritis it's impossible to swipe left.
姑娘们 今晚你们得负责打烊
Girls, you're going to have to close up tonight.
我挺确定我厄尔跟我"约"上了
I'm pretty sure I have a date with Earl.
阿憨 你唯一存在的非幻想友人来了
Han, your only friend that isn't imaginary is here.
他是来给我送游戏展贵宾票
He's dropping my VIP passes to Game Con.
内德要展出他做出的全新电玩
Ned's demo-ing the brand new video game he created,
我要去看
and I'll be there
然后跟玩角色扮演的妹子们厮混
hanging out in the cosplayer's lair.
去那里被"撕"又"混"不上床吗
Is that where you don't get laired?
幸好我没告诉你赞助商是维珍[处子]公司
Thank God I didn't tell you it was sponsored by Virgin.
我对电玩理解无能
I don't get video games.
在我那年代 如果你想进入另一个虚拟现实
In my day, if you wanted to enter another reality
你只需要吃迷幻药 然后去水族馆就行了
you just took acid and went to the aquarium.
游戏展有很多超赞的礼包拿
Game Con has awesome swag bags.
今年他们会发苹果的平板
This year they're handing out iPads,
去年我拿到了微软的平板
and last year I got the Microsoft Surface.
你的确是个又"微"又"软"的平板
You are a micro-soft surface.
祝废柴电玩节玩得愉快
Have fun at Lollapa-loser.
打死我也不去死宅展
I would never go to Lame Con.
我绝对得去游戏展
I've got to go to Game Con!
好有更多嘲讽阿憨的机会吗
So we can make fun of Han some more?
嘲讽游戏宅真是我的嘲讽强项啊
Because video games really seem to be my put-down sweet spot.
卡洛琳 是时候让你知道了
Caroline, it's about time you knew.
我是电玩上瘾者
I'm really into video games.
我在10岁时发现这事
I've known since I was ten.
麦克斯 你是在出柜跟我坦白你是游戏宅女吗
Max, are you coming out to me as a game woman?
在我妈妈常把我
There was this arcade
扔在披萨店自生自灭 那里有游戏机房
at the pizza place my mom used to leave me at.
吃豆人教我怎么吞"药丸"
Ms. Pac-Man taught me how to swallow pills.
好吧 在这个开诚布公的时刻
All right, well, if we're confessing things,
我承认我超想要免费iPad
I really want a free iPad, so I guess
你估计得对那个阿宅好一点
you'll have to be nice to that nerd,
哪怕他是客人你也得忍着
even if he is a customer.
好的 我们能搞定
All right, we got this.
忍气吞声
Suck it up.
我啥也不想"吞"
I'm not sucking anything.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
原来"常言道"是真的有道理
Well, I guess it's true what they say.
常言道 别请你的美甲师
You can't hire my manicurist
来帮你的公寓搞装潢
to put an addition on your apartment, yeah.
你们在重新装潢啊
Oh, you're renovating.
难怪会听到有铁锤声跟电钻声
That explains the banging and power drills I hear.
大多数是我们自己搞的
Most of that was us.
我们买了一些新性爱玩具
We got some new sex toys.
家里简直就是圣诞老人的性爱玩具工厂
It's like Santa's dirty workshop up there.
我们打算把我闺房分成两半
See, we're splitting the boudoir in half
这样小孩也能有自己的房间
so the baby can have its own bedroom.
自己的房间
Its own bedroom?
所以你都还没怀上的那个孩子
So the baby that you're not even pregnant with yet
已经比卡洛琳大姐过得还好了吗
is doing better than old Caroline?
没 我的美甲师还想我改掉换衣间呢
No, Ming Wa wants me to give up my walk-in closet.
那可是我的包包跟我的假发住的地方
I mean, that's where my purses and half my hair live.
所以包包跟假发也过得比卡洛琳大姐好吗
So purses and hair are doing better than old Caroline too?
一块耳屎都过得比卡洛琳大姐好
Uh, earwax is doing better than old Caroline.
来吧 卡洛琳
Come on, Caroline.
屁股摇起来 门票拿过来
Let's shake these asses and get them passes.
你觉得我该为了明天的电玩展
Do you think I should shave my back
刮刮我的背毛吗
for tomorrow for Game Con?
我妈觉得有必要
My mom does.
这是你的薯条
Here are your fries.
内德 你最近在健身吗
Ned, have you been working out?
你居然知道我的名字
You know my name?
麦克斯 快把手拿开
Max, take your hand away.
他会爽"死"的
You'll kill him.
你有办法把我弄进明天的游戏展吗
Is there any way you can get me into Game Con tomorrow?
真是太超过了
Oh! This is rich.
辣妹想从宅男身上捞好处
The hot girls need something from the nerds
就像科学课 或洛杉矶所有的婚姻一样
like in science class or any marriage in L.A.
我没有多余的票
I don't have any more tickets...
或者是活下去的勇气了
or now a will to live.
这下尴尬了
So... this is awkward.
青春期是比较难熬 阿憨
Well, puberty's a challenging time, Han.
我成功了
I did it!
我把咱们搞进去了
I got us in.
麦克斯 我真心觉得我们去住
Max, again, I feel like the homeless shelter
流浪汉之家会是一种退步
would be a step down for us.
是搞进电玩展
To Game Con.
我弄到了展场辣妹的工作
I got us jobs as booth babes!
我宁愿去住流浪汉之家
I'd rather go to the shelter.
展场辣妹是什么鬼
What are booth babes?
我们只需要穿上这个裙子
We just have to wear these dresses,
打扮妖艳 然后发传单就行了
look hot, and hand out some flyers.
就跟是性感版的传教士
Like a sexy Jehovah's Witness.
穿那个吗
Wearing that?
-上身在哪 -这就是上身啊
- Where's the top? - That is the top.
-好吧 那下身呢 -你正看着呢
- Okay, where's the bottom? - You're looking at it.
-那中间部分呢 -就这个
- Where's the middle? - That's it.
-其他部分呢 -对哦
- And the rest? - Oh, right.
骚气长靴
Slutty boots!
我们真的要为了一个礼包露"小妹妹"吗
Are we really gonna show our vaginas for a gift bag?
当然 不然要"她"何用
Yes, what else are they for?
你也听到阿憨说的了
You heard Han.
可能可以拿到电视 游戏机 你心爱的iPad
We could get a TV, XBoxes, your precious iPad.
或者至少能捞到一瓶瓶装水
At the very least, bottled water.
我只是觉得穿着短裙走来走去给人看
It's just so degrading to parade around in short skirts
还得对宅男们假亲切很...
and be fake nice to nerds and...
靠 这就是我们在餐厅就是干这个的
Oh, my God, that's what we do at the diner.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我们不得不炒了我们的承包商
We had to fire our contractor.
他搞半天都没成果
Yeah, it's just taking too long.
就跟吃了百忧解的软男做爱一样
It's like having sex with a guy on Prozac.
同是天涯沦落人
Been there.
等到现在还没"爽"呢
And I'm still waiting.
所以我们雇了我表姐
So we hired my cousin.
我们分手之后关系反而变好了
She and I have become close since we stopped dating.
我们本来打算去住酒店
I mean, we were going to stay at a hotel,
但我们能跟朋友住 又何须去酒店呢
but why do that when we can stay with friends?
朋友 哪来的朋友
Friends? What friends?
不是说你卡洛琳 是麦克斯
Not you, Caroline. Max.
真不敢相信我穿成这样
I can't believe what I'm wearing.
这衣服比电视剧《球手》还贬低女性
This dress sets women back further than HBO's "Ballers."
我觉得难得有人付钱让我穿上衣服很好啊
Well, I think it's nice to be paid to put on clothes for once.
拿一份传单吗
"Ant Thrax"?
您得自己弯腰拿
You'll have to get it.
我不能再弯了
I can't bend over any further
否则我的"游戏机"就要露出来了
or everyone will see my PlayStation.
咱们这展点刚发生超慢速地震了吗
Did a very slow earthquake just hit this booth?
您好 请问这是真的舞步
Hi. Is this, like, a real dance,
还是病发作需要救护车
or should I go get help?
她们不是癫痫发作
They're not having seizures.
我们好像也应该这么跳起来
I think we're supposed to dance like that.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max? Caroline?
尽管你刚才看到我们那样
Even though you just saw us doing that,
我们还是比你酷太多了
we are still so much cooler than you.
是啊 但是差距已经越来越小
Yes, but the gap's getting smaller.
你们两个怎么进来的[到这一步]
How did you two get in here?
感谢一路上无数的错误决定
A continuing series of bad decisions.
你不帮我们
You wouldn't help us,
所以我们决定来当展场辣妹
so we decided to be booth babes.
无数的错误决定中 最新的一个错误
The most recent in the continuing series of those bad decisions.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 介绍给你们我的玩家小伙伴
Max, Caroline, I'd like you to meet my gamer crew.
我的憨兵卫
Basically, my Han-tourage.
你没说错 这绝对是处男[维珍]赞助的
You were right, this thing was sponsored by Virgin.
如果你们都来这里了
If you guys are here,
你们在奶奶家地下室的老窝是谁在照看
who's watching your grandmother's basements?
这位是我的女伴 尤妮斯
And this is my plus-one, Eunice.
又名"超级任舔糖"
AKA Super Nintend-Ho.
我们今天是首次见面
We never met till today.
他是不是超萌啊
Isn't he the cutest?
他把我从大火弥漫的村庄中救出来
He saved me from a burning village,
然后他就跟我求婚了
and then he asked me to marry him.
其实是我的角色
Actually, my avatar asked
跟她的角色求婚了
her avatar to get married...
游戏里结婚
in the game.
恭喜恭喜
Congratulations.
这一点都不可悲
That's not sad.
我去给我的小萌物买杯喝的
I'm gonna go get my Pixel Pie a drink.
这是小女子对将我从
It's the least I can do for the man
咆哮炼狱中救出的英雄的小小报答
who pulled me from a roaring inferno.
快去快回
Hurry back!
我真应该让她被烧死
I should have let her burn!
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
她不就是你的理想型吗
She's your type:
饿虎扑羊
willing.
但我不想放弃一片森林啊
But I can't be tied down.
有着这贵宾票
Between this VIP pass
跟我在假日快捷酒店开好的房间
and my suite at the Holiday Inn Express,
我能成为游戏展的西门庆呢
I could be the Don Juan of Game Con.
她来了
She's coming!
我的憨·索罗[星战角色]去哪了
Oh, where's Han Solo going?
《神奇宝贝》的展场有快闪族活动
Uh... the Pokemon booth started a flash mob
他们需要一只皮卡丘
and they needed a Pikachu.
死神婊
Death Bitch!
我就觉得你很眼熟
I knew you seemed familiar.
你长得就像那个新角色"死神婊"
You look like that new character, Death Bitch.
你的展厅就在那边
Your booth is right over there.
是这个展场第二热门的游戏了
It's the most popular video game here...
第一是"虚拟女朋友"
after "Girlfriend Simulator."
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max.
你看
Look.
阿憨的游戏宅友要把你抱走了
Han's gamer friend nerd is carrying you away.
而且我对他手放的位置很有意见
And I do not like where he has his hand.
内德 不许走
Ned, stop!
对啊
Yeah.
起码先请我喝杯酒再这样
At least buy me drink first.
我就把这个放下
I'm just gonna put this down.
内德 这是你的游戏吗
Ned, this is your game?
你把麦克斯变成了巨乳女侠之类的人物
You turned Max into some kind of Boobarella.
对不起 你们本不该现在就看到
I'm sorry, you weren't supposed to see this yet.
我本来打算邀请你们参加正式发行派对
I was going to invite you to the official release party.
如果这男的要有发行[射]派对
If this guy's having a release party,
那也是对着袜子里射[自慰]
it's probably into an old sock.
对了 这个我要拿走
By the way, I'm taking this.
我需要有人顶替我明天餐厅的班
I need someone to cover my shift at the diner tomorrow.
我觉得你再也不需要在餐厅工作了
I don't think you'll need to work at the diner
因为内德盗用了你的肖像权
after you're compensated for Ned stealing your likeness.
我妈说这没事啊
My mom said it was fine.
我能因为这个捞到钱吗
I can get money for this?
我蛮确定
Because I'm pretty sure
《侠盗猎车手》是抄袭我怎么去纽约的故事
"Grand Theft Auto" is based on how I got to New York.
两位姑娘好
How you doing?
托尼·夏皮罗 摇滚游戏公司
Tony Shapiro, Rock N' Roll Games.
最近刚刚离婚
Recently divorced.
托尼 我觉得你不会想跟一位
Tony, I don't think you bargained for
受过沃顿教育的展场辣妹讨价还价
a Wharton-educated booth babe...
我也不会
and neither did I.
但贵公司的设计师未经过我朋友同意
But your designer stole my friend's likeness
盗用她的肖像权
without her consent,
所以我们有权获得一定比例的收益
so we're entitled to a percentage of the profits.
这幅画没有那么像她 就算到了法庭
This illustration is not so similar that it would hold up
我们也站得住脚
in a court of law.
我的老天 死神婊
Oh, my God, Death Bitch.
那不是她
That's not her.
不是才有鬼咧
The hell it's not.
瞧瞧她 伙计
Look at her, dude.
一个两个 货真价实
One, two.
很明显你们俩没有钱请律师
Look, it's clear you guys don't have the money for a lawyer.
那倒是 继续说
That's true. Keep talking.
但我懂你们想赚点小钱
But I get you want a payday,
所以我会付钱请你的朋友扮演阿莫拉
so I will pay your friend to play Amorta
明天在我们的拍照展位跟粉丝们合影
and take pictures with the fans at our photo booth tomorrow.
算你们走运
You're in luck.
我们之前请的模特死于吸毒过量
The model we hired died of an overdose.
至少她是死于我钟爱的事情
At least she died doing what I love.
托尼 或许我们看起来像是不得不认命的人
Tony, we may look like we've settled in life,
但这件事我们一定抗争到底
but we aren't gonna settle here.
如果闹到法庭上 我们肯定要分几百万
We stand to make millions if we take you to court.
-不会的 -那倒是 继续说
- No, you don't. - That's true, keep talking.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
送一个免费iPad
Throw in a free iPad
我会准时把她干净送到
and I'll deliver her on-time and clean.
你会准时把我送到
You'll get me here on time.
这是闹哪出
Um... what's happening here?
是前戏 还是清理战场
Is this the foreplay or the cleanup?
苏菲用磨脚器帮我磨脚呢
Sophie's using a PedEgg on my feet.
好痒啊
And it tickles.
对啊 如果你放任自己一天
Yeah, you know, if you go just one day
没有磨脚上的老茧
without shaving calluses,
那你就满盘皆输了
you've already lost the war.
不好意思 把屋子弄得乱糟糟
Yeah, well, I'm sorry for the mess.
我必须把一些日常必需品带下来
Uh, I had to bring down some basic necessities.
比如盘子和杯子 还有厕纸
Yeah, like... like plates and cups and toilet paper.
等等 我公寓里是有一台电视和游戏机吗
Wait, is that a TV and an XBox in my apartment?
我都激动得不知所措了
I don't know what to do.
我这辈子都在等这一天
I've been waiting for this day my whole life,
而现在实现了 我却害羞了
and now that it's here I'm shy.
没错 我们就是这么看电视
Yeah, this is how we watch TV.
我们有葫芦网 奈飞网 油管网
We get Hulu, Netflix, YouTube...
打屁屁网
YouSpank...
打屁屁大全网
SpankBank...
色情棒子网
PornOnTheCob.
我能试试今天拿的这张试玩游戏光盘吗
Can I pop in this sweet demo game I got today?
这是超性感超暴力版的我
It's a hyper-sexualized, violent version of me
顺我者昌 逆我者亡
who kills everyone who gets in my way.
说真的 这就是我的传记电影
It's a biopic, really.
插进去 我来看你玩
Stick it in and I'll watch you play.
老天 如果他每次说这话我就有五分钱
Gosh, if I had a nickel every time Oleg said that...
那你们现在就够钱住酒店了吗
You'd be able to afford a hotel room?
好吧 我要去另一间房
Okay, well, I'm gonna go in the other room,
远离这里
anywhere but here...
虽然那房现在有股广藿香和波兰饺子味儿
which now smells like patchouli and pierogis.
我们房里都有性爱秋千了
Oh, we have a sex swing now.
欢迎来到艾斯里瑟 阿莫拉
Welcome to Asrieth, Amorta.
你必须杀掉一切会动的东西
You must kill anything that moves.
开始吧
Go.
这妞简直是我的精神野兽
This chick is my spirit animal.
她做的不过是喝酒壶里的酒
All she's doing is drinking from a flask
然后一拳揍人脸上
and punching people in the face.
麦克斯 她超像你
Max, she's just like you.
牦牛妹 快来
Yak Girl, come!
我需要你
I need you!
那个傻逼的动物是什么
What's that silly animal thing?
牦牛妹
Yak Girl.
我觉得她是我的伙伴
I think she's my sidekick.
那玩意看起来超像卡洛琳
That thing looks just like Caroline.
的确
It does!
它看起来像卡洛琳
It looks like Caroline!
为什么我听见了我的名字
Why did I hear my name?
为什么我看见一匹马长了我的脸
Why am I seeing a horse thing that has my face?
拜托 卡洛琳 这不是一匹马长了你的脸
Please, Caroline, it's not a horse thing with your face.
是一头牦牛长了你的脸
It's a yak thing with your face.
在餐厅每次让你
That's the sound you make
做一些琐碎的工作时 你就发出这声音
when you have to do side work at the diner.
牦牛妹 快来
Yak Girl, come!
瞧瞧
Hey, look.
麦克斯 你在骑她耶
Max, you're riding her.
不 不能这样
Oh, no, no way.
我现在就要打给那个叫托尼的混蛋
I'm calling that Tony jerk right now.
现在是怎样
So what?
她就乖乖让死神婊骑她吗
She just lets Death Bitch ride her?
牦牛妹难道就这一个功能吗
That's all Yak Girl does?
不啊 当一按这个按钮 她就会拉屎
No, she poops when you hit this button.
卡洛琳 屎不停
Ah, Caroline can't stop pooping!
就像某次在餐厅时那样
Just like that one time at the diner.
托尼 我是卡洛琳·钱宁
Tony, this is Caroline Channing,
又称牦牛妹
AKA Yak Girl.
我要把你告上法庭
I am taking you to court.
那倒是 继续说
That's true. Keep talking.
那就是你丰厚补偿吗
That's your big offer?
让我打扮成那样 跟阿宅们合影
That I dress like that and take pictures with nerds?
让我这么跟你说吧 先生
Well, let me just say to you, sir,
我还要一个免费iPad
I will need an iPad, as well.
某人最好快去拿厕纸哦
Somebody better go out and get that toilet paper.
死神婊还有多久才到
How long till Death Bitch?
我得先吃药
I have to go take my medication.
你吃什么药 可以分我点吗
What are you taking? You got any extra?
这边请
Right this way.
真是太让人兴奋了
This is so exciting.
这应该很好玩
This will be fun.
自从不在机动车管理局干后
I haven't been paid to be a bitch
很久没人花钱请我当婊子了
since I worked at the DMV.
哇 绿屏
Ooh, a green screen.
瞧 我在另一个星球
Look, I'm on another planet.
外太空的假期梦终于实现了
Finally got that vacation.
牦牛妹 快出来 时间就是金钱
Hey, Yak Girl, come on out. Time is money!
你在里面还好吗
You okay in there?
卡戴珊在别人面前亮相时肯定也是这感觉
This is what it must be like for Kim Kardashian to enter a room.
好了 流程很简单
All right, it's pretty simple.
合影一张
One picture.
如果你"硬"了 别担心
And don't worry if you get a boner.
我们会改图去掉它
We'll crop it out.
我还能再丢脸一点吗
Could I be any more humiliated?
我只想跟她合影
I just want a photo with her.
不是你
Not you.
我猜你能
I guess you could.
好吧 我估计是来表演拉屎的
Fine, I'm probably due for a poop, anyway.
我没事
I'm okay!
你能把我头砍掉吗
Can you chop my head off?
你此生有戏得到的最佳砍头[口交]
It'll be the best head you'll ever get.
好了 快滚 我已经杀死你了
All right, get out of here. I killed you.
等等
Hold on.
死神婊 说你的招牌口头禅
Death Bitch, say your catchphrase.
记住 即使在冥界
Remember: even in death,
你仍是我的小婊砸
you're my bitch.
我真的好喜欢这个身份
I'm really liking this identity.
这比我另外17个身份好多了
It's better than the other 17 I've had.
没人想跟我合影
Nobody wants to take a photo with me.
拜托 姐可是牦牛啊 对吧 麦克斯
I mean, baby got yak, right, Max?
你就不能让我享受这身份吗
Will you just let me enjoy this?
这对我来说 就是梦想成真
This is a dream come true for me.
我在一个游戏展上
I'm at a game convention.
我是一个电子游戏里的明星
I'm the star of a video game.
我可以不顾后果大开杀戒
I can kill without consequences.
我现在几乎就是人生巅峰啊
I'm pretty much peaking right now.
是啊 而我有蹄子
Yeah, well, I have hooves.
我就不能难过一分钟吗
Can I just be upset for one minute?
麦克斯 快把我藏起来
Max, hide me.
貌似你的隐藏技能已经很厉害了
Looks like you're doing a pretty good job of that yourself.
别闹了 快救命
Seriously, help.
快回来 憨·索罗
Get back here, Han Solo!
你答应我要跟我一起生活
You promised we'd build our lives together.
我们也有过"小姐上流氓"式分食速食派了
We shared that Hot Pocket "Lady in the Tramp" style.
这位小姐
Uh, miss?
肯定有比他更好的男人
There's gotta be better people out there.
你没跟"任何男人"试过吗
Have you tried literally anyone else?
我说服我姐姐签字让精神病院放我出来
I convinced my sister to sign me out for this weekend,
所以你决不能阻止我见我的阿憨
so you are not gonna stop me from seeing my Han.
闪开 阿莫拉
Back off, Amorta!
阿憨 你得靠自己了
Uh, Han, you're on your own.
我不能毁了这身戏服
I can't ruin this costume.
我下次想逃脱陪审团职责时 还得靠这身衣服
I'm gonna need it the next time I have to get out of jury duty.
天啊 我死定了
Oh, no, I'm a goner.
她肯定会把我生吞活剥
She's gonna eat me alive.
你们没看到共食速食派时 她差点把我搞怀孕的样儿
You should have seen her go to town on that Hot Pocket.
走开 阿憨 我证明给大家看
Out of the way, Han. I'll show you all
我能做的不光是拉屎
I can do more than just poop.
牦牛妹
Uh, Yak Girl?
你的屁屁部位露出来了
Your heinie quarters are showing.
拍到了
Got it.
这肯定会让我在网上骗的那个妹子吃醋
This is gonna make the girl I'm catfishing real jealous.
厄尔
Hey, Earl.
卡洛琳 麦克斯
Hey, Caroline. Hey, Max.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
你好 麦克斯
Hi, Max. Hey.
瞧瞧
Look at that.
我有一副一模一样的鹿角
I have the exact same antlers.
那不是我
That's not me.
看她移动速度这么快就知道了
You can tell by how fast she's moving.
你知道什么不快吗
Know what's not moving fast?
我们家的装修
Our construction.
对 我们不得不解雇奥列格的表姐
Yeah, we had to fire Oleg's cousin.
事实证明 性的吸引力还在
Turns out the sexual tension was still there.
而她当年的肉体...不复存在
Her body... not so much.
是呀 所以至少还要一周的时间
Yeah, so it's gonna take at least another week.
一周吗
A week?
"麦与卡醒着时不爱爱"的原则我可不守了
There goes the "No sex while Max and Caroline are awake" rule.
你们在我俩面前搞得那样居然还不算做爱
That wasn't sex you were having in front of us?
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Max, Caroline,
我不知道该如何报答你俩
I don't know how I'll ever repay you
替我摆脱尤妮斯的恩情
for getting Eunice off my back.
我知道
I do.
苏菲和奥列格会去你家住一周
Sophie and Oleg are staying at your place for a week.
我本想着是工作餐多加一个烤土豆呢
I was thinking an extra baked potato with your shift meal.
对了 阿憨
Yeah, Han, um...
你家的床能承受多大强度的"蹦跶"
how much bouncing can your bed take?
你真是要了我的命 麦克斯
You're killing me, Max.
是的 即使在冥界
Yep, even in death,
你仍是我的小婊砸
you're my bitch.